[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 5, "question": "What about stronger gun laws?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "stronger", "gun", "laws", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "That won't help.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "wo", "n't", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Because criminals don't care about the gun laws.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "criminals", "do", "n't", "care", "about", "the", "gun", "laws", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Was there anything in your encounter with this particular cat which made you feel that there may be a problem down the line?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "anything", "in", "your", "encounter", "with", "this", "particular", "cat", "which", "made", "you", "feel", "that", "there", "may", "be", "a", "problem", "down", "the", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "No, there was no indication when I was in the case, in the enclosure with Couscous, you know, that -- you know, made me feel uncomfortable or -- you know, I didn't see any type of aggressive behavior or anything that I needed to be worried about while I was in with him.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "there", "was", "no", "indication", "when", "I", "was", "in", "the", "case", ",", "in", "the", "enclosure", "with", "Couscous", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "--", "you", "know", ",", "made", "me", "feel", "uncomfortable", "or", "--", "you", "know", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "see", "any", "type", "of", "aggressive", "behavior", "or", "anything", "that", "I", "needed", "to", "be", "worried", "about", "while", "I", "was", "in", "with", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Were there any issues about security, about perhaps the level of training for the staff there?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "there", "any", "issues", "about", "security", ",", "about", "perhaps", "the", "level", "of", "training", "for", "the", "staff", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "So, Dale, How much food does he eat every day?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "Dale", ",", "How", "much", "food", "does", "he", "eat", "every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "RB", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "He eats about eight pounds of food a day.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "eats", "about", "eight", "pounds", "of", "food", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dale"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Do you have a lion by the tail?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "lion", "by", "the", "tail", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Just today.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "In terms of the intern who has died here, would you have expected somebody who was simply an intern to be inside the cage?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "intern", "who", "has", "died", "here", ",", "would", "you", "have", "expected", "somebody", "who", "was", "simply", "an", "intern", "to", "be", "inside", "the", "cage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "You know, Piers, I really don't know the circumstances but I can tell you that my interaction over at Project Survival Cat Haven, they've been very professional and you know, they've always run their protocol very strictly.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "circumstances", "but", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "that", "my", "interaction", "over", "at", "Project", "Survival", "Cat", "Haven", ",", "they", "'ve", "been", "very", "professional", "and", "you", "know", ",", "they", "'ve", "always", "run", "their", "protocol", "very", "strictly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And from what have gleaned, what do you think may have happened here?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "what", "have", "gleaned", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "may", "have", "happened", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, obviously, it's a shock anytime someone loses a life like this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "obviously", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "shock", "anytime", "someone", "loses", "a", "life", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Or would it be a more defensive mechanism if they felt that somebody was intruding into their space?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "would", "it", "be", "a", "more", "defensive", "mechanism", "if", "they", "felt", "that", "somebody", "was", "intruding", "into", "their", "space", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, depending on how long this girl had been there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "depending", "on", "how", "long", "this", "girl", "had", "been", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "What is your answer to people who say they shouldn't be in captivity (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "answer", "to", "people", "who", "say", "they", "should", "n't", "be", "in", "captivity", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, the point is, Piers, in the zoological world, they're there.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "point", "is", ",", "Piers", ",", "in", "the", "zoological", "world", ",", "they", "'re", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "And, Jenny, final word from you?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "Jenny", ",", "final", "word", "from", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "You know, my thoughts and prayers go out to the family of this young woman.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "my", "thoughts", "and", "prayers", "go", "out", "to", "the", "family", "of", "this", "young", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jenny"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What is your reaction to what's happening?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "what", "'s", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "It is an interesting moment because there has always been this contingent of civil libertarians in Congress that the military way overstretches their bounds and crosses boundaries in terms of what they can do.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "an", "interesting", "moment", "because", "there", "has", "always", "been", "this", "contingent", "of", "civil", "libertarians", "in", "Congress", "that", "the", "military", "way", "overstretches", "their", "bounds", "and", "crosses", "boundaries", "in", "terms", "of", "what", "they", "can", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What is the difference really, other than drones sound scarier about the ability to use a drone?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "difference", "really", ",", "other", "than", "drones", "sound", "scarier", "about", "the", "ability", "to", "use", "a", "drone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, that is a good point, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "a", "good", "point", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Because if it is okay to assassinate American citizens in Pakistan for grievous offenses against the state, what is the difference really between doing it there or doing it in Texas?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "if", "it", "is", "okay", "to", "assassinate", "American", "citizens", "in", "Pakistan", "for", "grievous", "offenses", "against", "the", "state", ",", "what", "is", "the", "difference", "really", "between", "doing", "it", "there", "or", "doing", "it", "in", "Texas", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "OPPINS: Right.", "answer_tokens": ["OPPINS", ":", "Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Pakistan", "Texas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "And that shocked a lot of people, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "shocked", "a", "lot", "of", "people", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "That's the issue here is the hedging on that very specific question that most people if you asked them will shake their head and think, my God, of course the government shouldn't be able to do that.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "issue", "here", "is", "the", "hedging", "on", "that", "very", "specific", "question", "that", "most", "people", "if", "you", "asked", "them", "will", "shake", "their", "head", "and", "think", ",", "my", "God", ",", "of", "course", "the", "government", "should", "n't", "be", "able", "to", "do", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "B, what do you think his lasting legacy with Fox News will be?", "question_tokens": ["B", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "his", "lasting", "legacy", "with", "Fox", "News", "will", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["LS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "Well, on the first question, he's definitely worth a biography or two.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "on", "the", "first", "question", ",", "he", "'s", "definitely", "worth", "a", "biography", "or", "two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fox News"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "For what?", "question_tokens": ["For", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "They were automatic weapons, had silencers on them.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "automatic", "weapons", ",", "had", "silencers", "on", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Did you ever kill anyone?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "kill", "anyone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "That I can't answer.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "I", "ca", "n't", "answer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Right now, the people that are in your circle, are they illegally trafficking guns?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "the", "people", "that", "are", "in", "your", "circle", ",", "are", "they", "illegally", "trafficking", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "RB", ",", "CC", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "How do they do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "they", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "They have people that are elderly, husband and wife or husband and girlfriend or whatever, in a motor home.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "people", "that", "are", "elderly", ",", "husband", "and", "wife", "or", "husband", "and", "girlfriend", "or", "whatever", ",", "in", "a", "motor", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "An elderly husband and wife hide guns in their motor home, and drive them up from Florida to New York?", "question_tokens": ["An", "elderly", "husband", "and", "wife", "hide", "guns", "in", "their", "motor", "home", ",", "and", "drive", "them", "up", "from", "Florida", "to", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "So what is an average load?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "is", "an", "average", "load", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Two cases.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "cases", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["5,000 dollars"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "How much would they make?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "would", "they", "make", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "They would make 5,000 dollars.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "would", "make", "5,000", "dollars", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "And this happens all the time?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "happens", "all", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "How do you communicate with one another to arrange the buy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "communicate", "with", "one", "another", "to", "arrange", "the", "buy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "CD", "DT", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "There's ways.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "ways", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What do you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I wanted to put them in jail, I would say yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "wanted", "to", "put", "them", "in", "jail", ",", "I", "would", "say", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "No?", "question_tokens": ["No", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What should they be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "they", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Life.", "answer_tokens": ["Life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Life?", "question_tokens": ["Life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Do you think that America, the government, is losing its war on guns?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "America", ",", "the", "government", ",", "is", "losing", "its", "war", "on", "guns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Because criminals don't care about the gun laws.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "criminals", "do", "n't", "care", "about", "the", "gun", "laws", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "How are these guns run?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "these", "guns", "run", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Any means of transportation, conveyance, planes, trains, automobiles.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "means", "of", "transportation", ",", "conveyance", ",", "planes", ",", "trains", ",", "automobiles", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Have you ever ridden a bus?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "ridden", "a", "bus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Have you never been searched getting on a bus?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "never", "been", "searched", "getting", "on", "a", "bus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "I mean, is that something you would like to see become illegal?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "that", "something", "you", "would", "like", "to", "see", "become", "illegal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "I can't comment on that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "comment", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "We enforce the laws that are on the books.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "enforce", "the", "laws", "that", "are", "on", "the", "books", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "You can't tell me what laws you think this country needs to make the streets safer?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "tell", "me", "what", "laws", "you", "think", "this", "country", "needs", "to", "make", "the", "streets", "safer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I would love to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "love", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Because we are so few and far between out there.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "are", "so", "few", "and", "far", "between", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "You wouldn't agree with mandating it?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "n't", "agree", "with", "mandating", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "No, absolutely not, because I don't -- like if you don't want to have a gun, lord knows I wouldn't want you to have a gun.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "absolutely", "not", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "like", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "have", "a", "gun", ",", "lord", "knows", "I", "would", "n't", "want", "you", "to", "have", "a", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Do you support universal background checks?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "support", "universal", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Look, I think it is OK if you want to have background checks on people when they buy and sell a gun.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "it", "is", "OK", "if", "you", "want", "to", "have", "background", "checks", "on", "people", "when", "they", "buy", "and", "sell", "a", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "But how do you know that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "how", "do", "you", "know", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "Because I know that they were already convicted criminals, who were already breaking the law by even owning a gun.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "know", "that", "they", "were", "already", "convicted", "criminals", ",", "who", "were", "already", "breaking", "the", "law", "by", "even", "owning", "a", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":"], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Why are you so keen to maintain the availability of what many see as a military style assault weapon?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "so", "keen", "to", "maintain", "the", "availability", "of", "what", "many", "see", "as", "a", "military", "style", "assault", "weapon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Because --", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "For the civilian population?", "question_tokens": ["For", "the", "civilian", "population", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "I don't see them as a military style.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "them", "as", "a", "military", "style", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "Isn't that responsible politics?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "responsible", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "This is my point.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "my", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Do you support all those?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "support", "all", "those", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I don't know if I support all of them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "support", "all", "of", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington", "D.C."]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "How do you know?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Because I think if you are not prosecuting the guys that are committing these crimes, if you're not having a background for mental health -- I mean, that is where I look at it and say, when they were dealing with mental health in Washington, D.C. right now, I'm all in favor of that, because there is a huge -- you want to talk about a loop hole, it is not the loop hole to buy guns on the black market that's a threat to this country.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "think", "if", "you", "are", "not", "prosecuting", "the", "guys", "that", "are", "committing", "these", "crimes", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "not", "having", "a", "background", "for", "mental", "health", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "is", "where", "I", "look", "at", "it", "and", "say", ",", "when", "they", "were", "dealing", "with", "mental", "health", "in", "Washington", ",", "D.C.", "right", "now", ",", "I", "'m", "all", "in", "favor", "of", "that", ",", "because", "there", "is", "a", "huge", "--", "you", "want", "to", "talk", "about", "a", "loop", "hole", ",", "it", "is", "not", "the", "loop", "hole", "to", "buy", "guns", "on", "the", "black", "market", "that", "'s", "a", "threat", "to", "this", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Who do you want to start with?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "want", "to", "start", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "I love them both.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "them", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Walker Bush"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "How did you feel about him attacking the president, the United States in the way that he did?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "about", "him", "attacking", "the", "president", ",", "the", "United", "States", "in", "the", "way", "that", "he", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "I didn't think that that was a good thing to do, because I love George Walker Bush, as you have seen in the tape.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "think", "that", "that", "was", "a", "good", "thing", "to", "do", ",", "because", "I", "love", "George", "Walker", "Bush", ",", "as", "you", "have", "seen", "in", "the", "tape", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger Ailes"]}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "What do you make of the debate about the affect that Fox News has had on American politics and American society?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "the", "debate", "about", "the", "affect", "that", "Fox", "News", "has", "had", "on", "American", "politics", "and", "American", "society", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Roger Ailes is a genius.", "answer_tokens": ["Roger", "Ailes", "is", "a", "genius", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fox News"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Is it case of two hopes, no hope and Bob Hope?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "case", "of", "two", "hopes", ",", "no", "hope", "and", "Bob", "Hope", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130306pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "Can he win?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "he", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Well, he can, but I don't think he will.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "can", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]